Florence Hollis and Rosemary Ross Reynolds Papers, 1863-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- OVERSIZE MATERIALS AND TAPES
  - Tapes of cases used in typology research
    - No. 1021
      - Reel 2
        - side 2, joint interview: Mr. Stridiron, interview 9; Mrs. Stridiron, interview 11, January 17, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Stridiron, interview 10; Mrs. Stridiron, interview 12, January 31, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mrs. Stridiron, interview 6, December 6, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Stridiron, interview 7, December 13, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, Mrs. Stridiron, interview 8, December 20, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Stridiron, interview 9, January 3, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, Mrs. Stridiron, interview 10, January 10, 1967 (Box 61)
    - No. 1022
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. Thompkins, interview 6, December 19, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Thompkins, interview 7, January 9, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. Thompkins, interview 6, December 15, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Thompkins, interview 7, December 23, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mrs. Thompkins, interview 8, January 6, 1967 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Thompkins, interview 9, January 13, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mrs. Thompkins, interview 10, January 18, 1967 (Box 61)
    - No. 1023
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mr. Moylan, interview 6, November 1, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Moylan, interview 7, November 8, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. Moylan, interview 6, November 7, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Moylan, interview 7, November 28, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mr. Moylan, interview 8, November 22, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Moylan, interview 9, November 29, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mr. Moylan, interview 10, December 14, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, Mrs. Moylan, interview 8, December 8, 1966 (Box 61)
        - side 2, joint interview: Mr. Moylan, interview 11; Mrs. Moylan, interview 9, December 21, 1966 (Box 61)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, joint interview: Mr. Moylan, interview 12; Mrs. Moylan, interview 10, January 5, 1967 (Box 61)
    - No. 1024
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mrs. Frye, interview 6, December 19, [1966?] (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Frye, interview 7, January 9, [1967?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. Frye, interview 8, January 16, [1967?] (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Frye, interview 9, January 30, [1967?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mrs. Frye, interview 10, February 6, [1967?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 4
        - side 1, Mr. Frye, interview 6, January 5, [1967?] (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Frye, interview 7, January 12, [1967?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 5
        - side 1, Mr. Frye, interview 8, January 19, [1967?] (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mr. Frye, interview 9, January 26, [1967?] (Box 61)
      - Reel 6
        - side 1, Mr. Frye, interview 10, February 2, [1967?] (Box 61)
    - No. 1025
      - Reel 1
        - side 1, Mrs. Michael, interview 6, March 30, 1967 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Michael, interview 7, April 6, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 2
        - side 1, Mrs. Michael, interview 8, April 13, 1967 (Box 61)
        - side 2, Mrs. Michael, interview 9, April 20, 1967 (Box 61)
      - Reel 3
        - side 1, Mrs. Michael, interview 10, April 27, 1967 (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous tape (used in research?) 62-A, School of Social Welfare, University of California, Berkeley, May 15, 1963 (Box 61)
    - Correspondence records, Rosemary Reynolds, 1949-1984 (Box 62)
  - Research project proposal, charts, Community Service Society of New York, 1974 (Mapcase Flat file)